(Wil:)It's my last one.
I want you to have it.
(Sheldon:)Look, everyone.
Wil Wheaton is my friend!
(Brent Spiner:)Oh, wow. I haven't seen
one of these in years.
(Brent Spiner:)Remember how we used to make these
things look like they were masturbating?
(Sheldon:)Brent Spiner, what have you done?
That was a mint-in-package
Wesley Crusher action figure.
(Sheldon:)Signed by my close personal friend,
Wil Wheaton.
(Brent:)Sorry, Slim. I've got some Mr. Data dolls
in the trunk of my car.
(Brent:)You want me to sign one for you?
(Sheldon:)You've already signed something,
Brent Spiner.
(Sheldon:)Your name on my list.
(Sheldon:)From this moment on,
you are my mortal enemy.
(Wil:)Don't worry. It doesn't take up
a whole lot of your time.
(Sheldon:)Come on, buddy. Let's not waste
another second on this loser.
(Sheldon:)Love your house.
- Can we get autographed dolls?
- Sure.
(Brent:)Twenty bucks.
(Stuart:)Ten.
- Eighteen.
- Twelve.
- Sixteen.
- Two for 30.
(Leonard:)And you come to my birthday party.
(Howard:)Done.